export default [
{
            id: 1,
            question: 'What is 10 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['18','19','20','17'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is 10 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['21','20','18','19'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 3,
            question: 'What is 10 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['21','22','20','19'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 4,
            question: 'What is 10 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['21','22','20','23'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 5,
            question: 'What is 10 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['24','21','23','22'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 6,
            question: 'What is 10 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['22','23','24','25'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 7,
            question: 'What is 10 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['26','25','23','24'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 8,
            question: 'What is 10 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['25','26','27','24'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is 10 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['25','27','26','28'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 10,
            question: 'What is 10 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['28','29','27','26'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 11,
            question: 'What is 11 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['10','11','9','8'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 12,
            question: 'What is 11 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['11','10','12','9'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 13,
            question: 'What is 11 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['10','13','11','12'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 14,
            question: 'What is 11 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['12','14','13','11'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 15,
            question: 'What is 11 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['12','15','13','14'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 16,
            question: 'What is 11 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['15','16','14','13'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 17,
            question: 'What is 11 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['15','16','17','14'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 18,
            question: 'What is 11 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['16','15','17','18'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 19,
            question: 'What is 11 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['18','16','17','19'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 20,
            question: 'What is 11 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['20','18','19','17'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 21,
            question: 'What is 11 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['21','19','20','18'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 22,
            question: 'What is 11 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['19','22','21','20'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 23,
            question: 'What is 11 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['22','23','21','20'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 24,
            question: 'What is 11 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['24','21','22','23'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 25,
            question: 'What is 11 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['23','22','24','25'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 26,
            question: 'What is 11 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['25','24','23','26'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 27,
            question: 'What is 11 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['24','25','26','27'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 28,
            question: 'What is 11 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['26','27','25','28'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 29,
            question: 'What is 11 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['29','28','26','27'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 30,
            question: 'What is 11 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['28','30','29','27'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 31,
            question: 'What is 12 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['10','11','9','12'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 32,
            question: 'What is 12 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['11','12','13','10'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 33,
            question: 'What is 12 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['14','12','13','11'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 34,
            question: 'What is 12 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['15','12','13','14'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 35,
            question: 'What is 12 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['16','15','13','14'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 36,
            question: 'What is 12 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['15','14','17','16'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 37,
            question: 'What is 12 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['16','17','15','18'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 38,
            question: 'What is 12 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['17','18','19','16'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 39,
            question: 'What is 12 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['20','18','17','19'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 40,
            question: 'What is 12 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['18','21','20','19'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 41,
            question: 'What is 12 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['22','20','21','19'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 42,
            question: 'What is 12 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['23','22','20','21'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 43,
            question: 'What is 12 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['24','23','22','21'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 44,
            question: 'What is 12 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['25','23','24','22'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 45,
            question: 'What is 12 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['25','24','23','26'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 46,
            question: 'What is 12 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['25','27','24','26'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 47,
            question: 'What is 12 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['25','28','26','27'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 48,
            question: 'What is 12 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['27','28','29','26'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 49,
            question: 'What is 12 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['30','27','28','29'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 50,
            question: 'What is 12 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['29','30','31','28'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 51,
            question: 'What is 13 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['10','13','11','12'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 52,
            question: 'What is 13 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['11','14','12','13'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 53,
            question: 'What is 13 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['15','13','14','12'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 54,
            question: 'What is 13 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['14','13','16','15'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 55,
            question: 'What is 13 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['16','15','17','14'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 56,
            question: 'What is 13 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['16','15','17','18'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 57,
            question: 'What is 13 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['18','16','19','17'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 58,
            question: 'What is 13 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['17','18','19','20'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 59,
            question: 'What is 13 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['19','18','21','20'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 60,
            question: 'What is 13 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['22','21','19','20'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 61,
            question: 'What is 13 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['21','20','22','23'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 62,
            question: 'What is 13 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['21','23','22','24'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 63,
            question: 'What is 13 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['25','23','22','24'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 64,
            question: 'What is 13 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['26','24','25','23'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 65,
            question: 'What is 13 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['26','27','24','25'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 66,
            question: 'What is 13 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['27','25','26','28'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 67,
            question: 'What is 13 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['29','28','27','26'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 68,
            question: 'What is 13 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['30','29','28','27'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 69,
            question: 'What is 13 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['28','29','31','30'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 70,
            question: 'What is 13 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['32','29','30','31'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 71,
            question: 'What is 14 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['11','13','14','12'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 72,
            question: 'What is 14 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['12','14','15','13'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 73,
            question: 'What is 14 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['14','15','13','16'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 74,
            question: 'What is 14 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['15','16','17','14'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 75,
            question: 'What is 14 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['17','18','15','16'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 76,
            question: 'What is 14 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['18','17','16','19'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 77,
            question: 'What is 14 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['18','20','19','17'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 78,
            question: 'What is 14 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['21','18','19','20'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 79,
            question: 'What is 14 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['20','21','22','19'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 80,
            question: 'What is 14 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['21','22','23','20'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 81,
            question: 'What is 14 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['22','21','23','24'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 82,
            question: 'What is 14 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['23','25','24','22'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 83,
            question: 'What is 14 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['24','23','26','25'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 84,
            question: 'What is 14 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['27','26','24','25'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 85,
            question: 'What is 14 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['26','27','25','28'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 86,
            question: 'What is 14 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['28','29','27','26'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 87,
            question: 'What is 14 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['29','28','30','27'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 88,
            question: 'What is 14 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['30','31','29','28'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 89,
            question: 'What is 14 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['30','29','31','32'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 90,
            question: 'What is 14 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['32','31','30','33'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 91,
            question: 'What is 15 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['15','12','14','13'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 92,
            question: 'What is 15 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['14','15','13','16'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 93,
            question: 'What is 15 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['17','16','14','15'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 94,
            question: 'What is 15 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['15','17','18','16'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 95,
            question: 'What is 15 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['19','16','18','17'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 96,
            question: 'What is 15 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['17','20','19','18'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 97,
            question: 'What is 15 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['21','18','19','20'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 98,
            question: 'What is 15 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['19','20','21','22'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 99,
            question: 'What is 15 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['20','23','21','22'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 100,
            question: 'What is 15 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['23','22','21','24'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 101,
            question: 'What is 15 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['24','22','25','23'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 102,
            question: 'What is 15 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['26','24','23','25'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 103,
            question: 'What is 15 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['25','24','27','26'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 104,
            question: 'What is 15 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['26','28','25','27'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 105,
            question: 'What is 15 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['29','26','27','28'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 106,
            question: 'What is 15 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['27','28','29','30'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 107,
            question: 'What is 15 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['31','30','28','29'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 108,
            question: 'What is 15 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['30','31','32','29'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 109,
            question: 'What is 15 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['31','32','30','33'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 110,
            question: 'What is 15 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['33','31','32','34'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 111,
            question: 'What is 16 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['16','15','14','13'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 112,
            question: 'What is 16 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['14','16','15','17'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 113,
            question: 'What is 16 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['16','18','17','15'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 114,
            question: 'What is 16 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['17','16','18','19'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 115,
            question: 'What is 16 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['19','18','20','17'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 116,
            question: 'What is 16 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['19','20','21','18'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 117,
            question: 'What is 16 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['21','19','22','20'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 118,
            question: 'What is 16 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['20','21','23','22'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 119,
            question: 'What is 16 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['21','23','24','22'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 120,
            question: 'What is 16 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['23','22','24','25'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 121,
            question: 'What is 16 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['26','25','24','23'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 122,
            question: 'What is 16 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['25','26','24','27'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 123,
            question: 'What is 16 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['27','28','25','26'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 124,
            question: 'What is 16 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['29','26','27','28'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 125,
            question: 'What is 16 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['28','30','29','27'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 126,
            question: 'What is 16 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['30','29','31','28'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 127,
            question: 'What is 16 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['32','31','29','30'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 128,
            question: 'What is 16 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['31','33','32','30'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 129,
            question: 'What is 16 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['32','31','34','33'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 130,
            question: 'What is 16 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['34','35','32','33'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 131,
            question: 'What is 17 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['16','14','15','17'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 132,
            question: 'What is 17 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['16','18','15','17'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 133,
            question: 'What is 17 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['16','17','19','18'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 134,
            question: 'What is 17 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['19','17','20','18'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 135,
            question: 'What is 17 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['18','20','21','19'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 136,
            question: 'What is 17 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['20','22','21','19'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 137,
            question: 'What is 17 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['22','21','23','20'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 138,
            question: 'What is 17 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['22','24','21','23'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 139,
            question: 'What is 17 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['25','23','24','22'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 140,
            question: 'What is 17 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['24','23','25','26'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 141,
            question: 'What is 17 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['26','27','25','24'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 142,
            question: 'What is 17 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['25','28','27','26'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 143,
            question: 'What is 17 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['29','28','27','26'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 144,
            question: 'What is 17 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['27','28','29','30'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 145,
            question: 'What is 17 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['28','29','31','30'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 146,
            question: 'What is 17 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['30','31','32','29'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 147,
            question: 'What is 17 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['33','31','32','30'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 148,
            question: 'What is 17 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['33','32','31','34'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 149,
            question: 'What is 17 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['35','33','34','32'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 150,
            question: 'What is 17 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['34','35','33','36'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 151,
            question: 'What is 18 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['17','18','16','15'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 152,
            question: 'What is 18 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['18','17','16','19'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 153,
            question: 'What is 18 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['17','19','18','20'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 154,
            question: 'What is 18 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['18','20','19','21'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 155,
            question: 'What is 18 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['21','22','19','20'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 156,
            question: 'What is 18 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['23','20','21','22'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 157,
            question: 'What is 18 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['24','21','22','23'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 158,
            question: 'What is 18 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['24','22','25','23'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 159,
            question: 'What is 18 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['24','26','23','25'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 160,
            question: 'What is 18 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['25','26','24','27'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 161,
            question: 'What is 18 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['25','27','26','28'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 162,
            question: 'What is 18 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['27','28','29','26'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 163,
            question: 'What is 18 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['28','29','27','30'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 164,
            question: 'What is 18 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['28','31','30','29'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 165,
            question: 'What is 18 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['30','32','31','29'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 166,
            question: 'What is 18 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['32','31','30','33'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 167,
            question: 'What is 18 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['32','34','31','33'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 168,
            question: 'What is 18 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['34','35','33','32'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 169,
            question: 'What is 18 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['34','33','35','36'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 170,
            question: 'What is 18 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['36','35','37','34'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 171,
            question: 'What is 19 + 0 ?',
            answers: ['19','18','16','17'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 172,
            question: 'What is 19 + 1 ?',
            answers: ['20','18','17','19'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 173,
            question: 'What is 19 + 2 ?',
            answers: ['20','21','19','18'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 174,
            question: 'What is 19 + 3 ?',
            answers: ['21','19','20','22'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 175,
            question: 'What is 19 + 4 ?',
            answers: ['23','21','22','20'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 176,
            question: 'What is 19 + 5 ?',
            answers: ['22','21','24','23'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 177,
            question: 'What is 19 + 6 ?',
            answers: ['24','25','23','22'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 178,
            question: 'What is 19 + 7 ?',
            answers: ['25','26','23','24'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 179,
            question: 'What is 19 + 8 ?',
            answers: ['26','24','27','25'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 180,
            question: 'What is 19 + 9 ?',
            answers: ['25','27','28','26'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 181,
            question: 'What is 19 + 10 ?',
            answers: ['27','26','29','28'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 182,
            question: 'What is 19 + 11 ?',
            answers: ['27','30','28','29'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 183,
            question: 'What is 19 + 12 ?',
            answers: ['28','29','31','30'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 184,
            question: 'What is 19 + 13 ?',
            answers: ['29','32','31','30'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 185,
            question: 'What is 19 + 14 ?',
            answers: ['33','32','30','31'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 186,
            question: 'What is 19 + 15 ?',
            answers: ['31','33','32','34'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 187,
            question: 'What is 19 + 16 ?',
            answers: ['32','34','33','35'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 188,
            question: 'What is 19 + 17 ?',
            answers: ['35','34','33','36'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 189,
            question: 'What is 19 + 18 ?',
            answers: ['34','36','35','37'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 190,
            question: 'What is 19 + 19 ?',
            answers: ['35','37','36','38'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
]
